{
    "subject": "resource/Sumeet_Raghavan",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/India",
    "human_readable": "Sumeet Raghavan was born in India.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9169211387634277,
            "question": "Where was Sumeet Raghavan born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8884298801422119,
            "question": "In what year was Sumeet Raghavan born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6219810247421265,
            "question": "What is Sumeet Raghavan known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46916481852531433,
            "question": "Does Sumeet Raghavan have any siblings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4062669575214386,
            "question": "Where does Sumeet Raghavan currently live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39793679118156433,
            "question": "What are some of Sumeet Raghavan's notable accomplishments?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3838806450366974,
            "question": "What kind of work is Sumeet Raghavan involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3254145681858063,
            "question": "Has Sumeet Raghavan received any awards or recognition?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31888630986213684,
            "question": "Is there anything unique about Sumeet Raghavan's upbringing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27257323265075684,
            "question": "What are some of Sumeet Raghavan's interests outside of work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sumeet Raghavan was born in India.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8498_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there anything unique about Sumeet Raghavan's upbringing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8498_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Sumeet Raghavan received any awards or recognition?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8498_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of work is Sumeet Raghavan involved in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8498_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8498_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8498_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8498_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8498_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8498_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8498_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8498_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8498_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8498_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8498_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all the documents mention Sumeet Raghavan's birthplace as Mumbai, Maharashtra, India."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references that confirm Sumeet Raghavan was born in Mumbai, Maharashtra, India. Therefore, the statement \"Sumeet Raghavan was born in India\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}